
let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: ": cos²θ/2+sin²θ/2 = ?",
      answer: "1",
      options: [
        "1/4",
        "1/2",
        "2",
        "1"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: " : If ƒ(x) = tan(x), then f <sup>-1</sup>(1/√(3)) =?",
      answer: "π/6",
      options: [
        "π/6",
        "π/4",
        "π/3",
        "π"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "The polar form of a complex number is :",
      answer: "r(cosθ + isinθ )",
      options: [
        "r ( tanθ + ιcotθ )",
        "r(secθ + ιcosecθ )",
        "r(cosθ + isinθ )",
        "r (sinθ + ιcosθ)"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "If ƒ(x) = √(x² +1), then domain of f is:",
      answer: "[-∞, ∞]",
      options: [
        "[-∞,-1]∪[1,∞]",
        "[-∞, ∞]",
        "[-∞,-2]∪[2,∞]",
        "[-∞,-2]∪[3,∞]"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "If ƒ(x) = √(x +1), then domain of f is:",
      answer: "[0,∞]",
      options: [
        "[0,∞]",
        "[-∞,0]",
        "[-∞, ∞]",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "If ƒ(x) = √(x² -1), then domain of f is:",
      answer: "[-∞,-1]∪[1,∞]",
      options: [
        "[-2,2]",
        "[-∞,-1]∪[1,∞]",
        "[-∞,-2]∪[2,∞]",
        "[-∞,-3]∪[3,∞]"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "sin²2θ =",
      answer: "1 - cos²2θ",
      options: [
        "1 - cos²θ",
        "1 + cos²θ",
        "1 - cos²2θ",
        "None"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "1 + cot²2θ/2 =",
      answer: "cosec²2θ",
      options: [
        "cosec²2θ",
        "cos²2θ",
        "sec²2θ",
        "None"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "3 x²+ 2 x + 1 is a",
      answer: "polynomial of degree 2",
      options: [
        "polynomial of degree 3",
        "polynomial of degree 2",
        "polynomial of degree 4",
        "None of these"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "A subset of B * A is called a ",
      answer: "Relation from B to A",
      options: [
        "Relation from B to A",
        "Relation from A to B ",
        "Relation in A",
        "None of these"
      ]
    }
  ];
  